Contact

989156179233 (Mobile) hosseinakbari506@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ hosseinakbari506 (LinkedIn) hosseinakbari506.ir (Personal)

Top Skills

PHP
JavaScript
HTML5 & CSS3

Languages

English (Limited Working)
Persian (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Rank of two provinces in Kharazmi Adolescent Festival

Hossein Akbari

Front-End Developer Iran

Summary

I'm a Front-End web developer and Video creator. I try to increase my knowledge and expertise every day and also try to do the project in the best quality. I work hard to apply my core knowledge of JavaScript combined with a keen interest in current and emerging technologies to make an effective solution.

Experience

Freelance, self-employed
Freelance Web Developer
June 2019 - Present (1 year 8 months)
Iran, Mashhad

Novinadmin Website Management September 2019 - January 2020 (5 months) Iran, Mashhad

My main job at Novin Admin was managing several news and corporate websites. Content production and SEO were also another part of my activities.

Education

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad)

High School, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2017 - 2020)